{
    "subject": "resource/Studio_7",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "\"Studio 7\" was also the original developmental title for the NBC drama Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip.Studio 7 is an American game show that aired on The WB during the summer of 2004.Studio 7 was hosted by NY1 anchor Pat Kiernan. Each episode featured seven contestants, mostly college-age, who lived together in New York City for the four days prior to the taping. During this time, they were given some of the material on which the show would quiz them. The show was promoted as a hybrid of game shows and reality television such as The Real World.The WB originally ordered two seasons of Studio 7, with the second season to air immediately after the first. However, the network cancelled plans for a second season during the initial run, due to low ratings.",
    "human_readable": "Studio 7 is an American game show that aired on The WB during the summer of 2004, hosted by Pat Kiernan, with contestants living together in New York City prior to the taping.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9416999816894531,
            "question": "Who hosted the game show Studio 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9201651215553284,
            "question": "Where did contestants live before taping Studio 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8766316771507263,
            "question": "What type of show was Studio 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.827539324760437,
            "question": "Was Studio 7 a popular show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6701293587684631,
            "question": "Where was Studio 7 filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6598467230796814,
            "question": "Which network broadcast Studio 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6573992967605591,
            "question": "What year did Studio 7 air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5643887519836426,
            "question": "What time of year did Studio 7 air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521083474159241,
            "question": "What was the general premise of Studio 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4841643273830414,
            "question": "Are there any reruns of Studio 7 available?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Studio 7 is an American game show that aired on The WB during the summer of 2004, hosted by Pat Kiernan, with contestants living together in New York City prior to the taping.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1407_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the general premise of Studio 7?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1407_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time of year did Studio 7 air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1407_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Studio 7 air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1407_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1407_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Studio 7 is an American game show, as it was aired on The WB and hosted by Pat Kiernan. Additionally, the documents mention that contestants lived together in New York City prior to the taping, which aligns with the triple's claim."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the triple. Studio 7 was indeed an American game show that aired on The WB from July 22, 2004, to September 2, 2004 (as mentioned in the document). It hosted Pat Kiernan and featured contestants living together in New York City prior to the taping of the show."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}